# DIME VAKANSKI



Wordpress Developer, Open Source Enthusiast, Instructor



I am a Wordpress / Web Developer with more than 10 years of experience coding for the Web. I have deep knowledge of PHP, MySQL, Web Services, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS3, JQuery, Vue.js, JavaScript, XML/RSS technologies and Open Source CMS's Wordpress and Drupal. I am also proficient in Marketing Operations as support to marketing teams to achieve the desired goals. Helping them Analyze and report data across multiple channels to monitor marketing site growth and Automate Marketing to Businesses. Creating landing pages, microsites, and Main-taining, optimizing all web assets to ensure compelling user experience. I have a deep understanding of Wordpress CMS with 7+ years experience developing themes, plugins and custom Wordpress orogramming & solid understanding of crossbrowser compatibility issues, W3C compatibility and SEO optimization

techniques.

### CONTACT



vakanski@gmail.com +38970223885

https://www.linkedin.com/in/vakanski/ https://github.com/vakanski



# **WORKING POSITIONS**

 Inteligenta, Skopje, Macedonia | Freelance Work | Digital Marketing Web Developer, Technical SEO

Sourcico, Tel Aviv, Israel | Full Time

Plannow Technologies, Vancouver, Canada/Freelance

Wordpress - Web Developer / Marketing Operations

Senior Web Developer

Freelance (UpWork) Web Developer

03.2019 - 10.2019

| 12.2016 - present

| 2010 - 2016

2007 - 2010



### Some of the projects I've worked on

#### Sealights Tech, https://www.sealights.io

Develop the backend & frontend of the website using Wordpress CMS php / mysql / html/ css / javascript/ JQuery / Salesforce Pardot / VWO / Optinmonster / Google Analytics / TagManager / Kathalon Studio QA [Technical owner]

#### HubSecurity, https://hubsecurity.io

Wordpress CMS / Elementor / php / mysql / html/ css / javascript/ JQuery / Google Analytics / Google Tag Manager / Hubspot / Mailchimp / Digital Ocean / Custom Theme Development

#### Homegrown Nursery, https://homegrownursery.com/

Wordpress CMS / Beaver Builder / php / mysql / html/ JQuery / Google Analytics / WooCommerce

#### Easy Imex, https://easyimex.com/

Wordpress CMS / Avada / php / mysql / html/ css / javascript/ JQuery / Google Analytics / Google Tag Manager UNIFONIC, www.unifonic.com

Develop the backend & frontend of the website using Wordpress CMS php / mysql / html/ css / javascript/ JQuery / Custom Jobs Plugin / Custom Theme Dev

#### KANDIDATE, www.kandidate.com

Develop the backend & frontend of the website using Wordpress CMS php / mysql / html/ css / javascript/ JQuery / Custom Theme Dev /

#### **BOEKME ADVENTURES, www.boekme.com**

Develop the backend & frontend of the website using Wordpress & WooCommerce php / mysql / html/ css / javascript/ JQuery / Paypal integration

The Deutsche Gesellschaft für Internationale Zusammenarbeit (GIZ), http://www.segrizime.gov.mk/

Develop the backend & frontend of the website using Drupal CMS

Sourcico, http://www.source.mk [Technical owner]

Headless CMS, using Wordpress API , Custom PHP/MySQL & Vue.js

Other Projects I've worked on: www.turbofalcon.ae, www.skywire.dk, www.languagedynamicsgroup.com, http://stonedesign.mk; http://meetbolo.com; http://www.ips.mk/, http://viewinn.mk, http://apimell.com/?lang=en, http://club4u.org.il, https://ting.com.mk/?lang=en, https://kurir.mk/, https://republika.mk/, https://rosacease.com, http://hometowndeals.ca,http://plannowtech.com, http://hub2europe.org/, http://memorialhouseofmotherteresa.org, https://lider.mk/, https://pressingtv.mk/, http://ting.com.mk/ +50 more projects



#### HARD PHP HTML **CSS JavaScript** Vue.js • • • • Wordpress MySQL

#### SOFT

communication skills self-awareness Team ability empathy conflict ability critical ability initiative 

time management



## **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATES**

2012-2015

Drupal

Bachelor of Computer Sciences, Faculty of Computer Science - University Goce Delcev, Shtip, Macedonia

Scrum Project Management Course Advanced Google Analytics Course by Google Web Applications for Everybody (4 courses taken on Coursera by University of Michigan) Web Design for Everybody (4 courses, taken on Coursera by University of Michigan) The Web Developer Bootcamp (Udemy)